[{"category":"History","id":"622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c5c","correctAnswer":"Macedon","incorrectAnswers":["Thrace","Epirus","Mycenae"],"question":"Alexander the Great was king of which kingdom?","tags":["history"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Science","id":"6243348ccfaae40c1296144e","correctAnswer":"A Joey","incorrectAnswers":["A Maggot","A Piglet","A Poult"],"question":"A young kangaroo is known as what?","tags":["science"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Science","id":"622a1c397cc59eab6f950fa0","correctAnswer":"Rabbits","incorrectAnswers":["Chickens","Pigs","Pigeons"],"question":"With Which Animals Do You Associate The Disease Myxomatosis?","tags":["animals","medicine","biology","science"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Science","id":"622a1c397cc59eab6f950fc0","correctAnswer":"Laslo Biro","incorrectAnswers":["Franz Bic","Henry Sheaffer","Pi√®rre Montblanc"],"question":"Who invented the ballpoint pen?","tags":[],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"History","id":"622a1c3c7cc59eab6f95189a","correctAnswer":"Russian","incorrectAnswers":["Indian","French","Egyptian"],"question":"What was the nationality of Rasputin?","tags":["people","history"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"History","id":"622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9518d4","correctAnswer":"St Petersburg","incorrectAnswers":["Kazan","Nizhny Novgorod","Moscow"],"question":"What Russian city was known as Leningrad between 1924 and 1991?","tags":["cities","russia","names","previous_names","history"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Science","id":"622a1c377cc59eab6f950509","correctAnswer":"the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study","incorrectAnswers":["relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees","cetaceans - whales, dolphins, and porpoise","a set of words and/or phrases, usually in relation to some particular canon or field of study"],"question":"What is Micrology the study of?","tags":["words","science"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"History","id":"62611f4e4b176d54800e3d50","correctAnswer":"1979","incorrectAnswers":["1967","1995","2002"],"question":"In which year was the Iranian Revolution?","tags":["events","the_middle_east","revolutions","history"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"History","id":"622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9517e4","correctAnswer":"Malta","incorrectAnswers":["Cyprus","Greece","Spain"],"question":"Which country was awarded The George Cross, the highest civilian award for bravery bestowed by the British government, in 1942?","tags":["history","world_war_2","uk","1940's"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"History","id":"62611f784b176d54800e3d5b","correctAnswer":"1969","incorrectAnswers":["1948","1955","1962"],"question":"In which year did the first human set foot on the moon?","tags":["events","firsts","space_exploration","space","cold_war","history"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"medium","regions":[],"isNiche":false}]